<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Healthy Life</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="paracetamol_decription">Paracetamol is a commonly used medicine that can help treat pain and reduce a high temperature (fever). It\'s typically used to relieve mild or moderate pain, such as headaches, toothache or sprains, and reduce fevers caused by illnesses such as colds and flu. Paracetamol is often recommended as one of the first treatments for pain, as it\'s safe for most people to take and side effects are rare.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_from_paracetamol">Side effects from paracetamol are rare but can include: an allergic reaction, which can cause a rash and swelling flushing, low blood pressure and a fast heartbeat – this can sometimes happen when paracetamol is given in hospital into a vein in your arm blood disorders, such as thrombocytopenia (low number of platelet cells) and leukopenia (low number of white blood cells) liver and kidney damage, if you take too much (overdose) – this can be fatal in severe cases Speak to a pharmacist or doctor if you develop any troublesome side effects that you think could be caused by paracetamol.</string>
    <string name="pudin_hara">Dabur Pudin Hara Active Antacid offers quick relief from stomach aches and bloating. It regulates bowel movement. Enriched with the goodness of medicinal herbs, it helps in treating the problem of gas and acidity. It promotes better digestion and helps get rid of common digestive disorders. Ayurvedic medicine is safe to administer for people of all age groups. This Dabur product offers relief from nausea, vomiting as well as discomfort caused due to overeating. The herbal medicine is also effective in lowering gastritis and gastroesophageal reflux disease symptoms. Dabur Pudin Hara price is quite reasonable.</string>
    <string name="pundin_hara_side_effect">No side effects of Dabur Pudin Hara have been reported in the medical literature. However, you should always consult your doctor before using Dabur Pudin Hara.</string>
    <string name="crocin">The Crocin Advance Tablet can be administered with another medication alone or in combination. As recommended by your doctor, you should take it regularly. It is typically better taken with food, otherwise, your stomach may become disturbed. Do not take more than prescribed or use it for longer. Side effects are uncommon if this medication is used properly, but in some individuals, this medicine can cause stomach pain, nausea, and vomiting.</string>
    <string name="crocin_side">When the body responds to the drug, most side effects don\'t require any medical treatment and vanish. If they continue or you are concerned about them, contact your doctor. Popular Adverse Effects are: Pain in the stomach Nausea Vomiting Over</string>
    <string name="evion">Evion 400 Capsule 10\'s contains Tocopherol (vitamin E), a fat-soluble vitamin that acts as an antioxidant with anti-inflammatory properties. It helps nourish and protect the skin from damage caused by free radicals. When there are too many free radicals accumulated in our body, it leads to various complications and diseases. Tocopherol (vitamin E) acts as an antioxidant which helps nourish and protect the skin from damage caused by free radicals. Thus it lowers chances of heart diseases, cancers, vision problems, and brain disorders.</string>
    <string name="evion_side">Overdose (more than 1200 mg/day) side effects: Headaches Dizziness Blurred vision Nausea Diarrhoea Flatulence Abdominal pain Rash Fatigue Weakness</string>
    <string name="vitamin_side">This medication contains vitamin D. Do not take Drisdol, Calciferol, cholecalciferol, 1,25-Dihydroxycholecalciferol, or ergocalciferol if you are allergic to vitamin D or any ingredients contained in this drug. Keep out of reach of children. In case of overdose, get medical help or contact a Poison Control Center immediately.</string>
    <string name="vitamin_d">Vitamin D supplements are commonly used to treat and prevent vitamin D deficiency. People who don\'t get enough sun and people who are 65 years or older are at risk for deficiency. People also use vitamin D for weak and brittle bones, heart disease, asthma, hay fever, and many other conditions, but there\'s no good scientific evidence to support many of these uses. There is also no strong evidence to support using vitamin D supplements for COVID-19.</string>
    <string name="amoxicillin">Amoxicillin is used to treat a wide variety of bacterial infections. This medication is a penicillin-type antibiotic. It works by stopping the growth of bacteria.This antibiotic treats only bacterial infections. It will not work for viral infections (such as common cold, flu). Using any antibiotic when it is not needed can cause it to not work for future infections.Amoxicillin is also used with other medications to treat stomach/intestinal ulcers caused by the bacteria H. pylori and to prevent the ulcers from returning.</string>
    <string name="amoxicillin_side">Abdominal or stomach cramps or tenderness back, leg, or stomach pains black, tarry stools bleeding gums blistering, peeling, or loosening of the skin bloating blood in the urine bloody nose chest pain chills clay-colored stools coughe</string>
    <string name="vakrasana">Vakrasana comes from a combination of two words, Vakra which means twisted and asana which means yoga posture. Vakrasana is among flexible yoga twist poses where twisting is observed in the spinal region and one may also call it a twisted pose or seated twist yoga pose.\n\n Although Vakrasana is a simple yoga for beginners it provides adequate stretch and twist to the spinal cord and lower abdomen region. The spinal twist yoga is practised in sitting posting and the trunk is twisted to either side.\n\n The twisted pose is beneficial for various body organs including liver, kidney, pancreas, ovary, testis, stomach and intestine. Vakrasana or the seated twist increases flexibility and burns the belly fat. Regular practice of Vakrasana benefits in case of diabetes.</string>
    <string name="sukhsana">Yogis have been practicing Sukhasana (Easy Pose) for centuries as a preferred posture for meditation. In many yogic traditions, the main purpose of Easy Pose is to drop into a meditative state. “Sukh” can also mean happy or joyful in Sanskrit, which is a feeling we hope to find within ourselves in a meditation practice. Sukhasana is one of the many paths to get there.\n\n Easy Pose may have been easy when you were a child, but as an adult,sitting cross-legged can be tricky. Our joints are no longer accustomed to the required rotation and flexibility, thanks to a chair-oriented culture that can cause tight hips and achy knees. Sitting in a chair for several hours a day encourages your body to lean back and sink into your midsection.\n\n If you work at a computer, you may lean forward and round your shoulders. Sukhasana, on the other hand, requires you to engage your core and back muscles to distribute your weight evenly over your sit bones. You also have to balance your shoulders over your hips and align your head with the rest of your spine. The pose helps stretch the hips and ankles, and strengthen back and abdominal muscles.</string>
</resources>